azstcu.org 2001-12-16

# Site Use Disclosure

|  |  **

PRIVACY NOTICE

**

Arizona State Savings & Credit Union, your member owned financial institution is committed to providing you financial products and services to meet your needs and reach your financial goals. 

We are equally committed to protecting our members’ privacy. You can be confident that your financial privacy is a priority of this credit union. We are required by law to give you this privacy notice to explain how we collect, use and safeguard your personal financial information. If you have any questions, please contact a member service representative at Arizona State Savings & Credit Union. 

**Information We Collect and Disclose About You**

 ****

We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications and other forms;
  * Information about your transactions with us or others;
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency;
  * Information obtained when verifying the information you provide on an application or other forms.

This may be obtained from your current or past employers, or from other institutions where you conduct financial transactions. We may disclose all information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. To protect our members’ privacy we only work with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information we provide. We do not permit these companies to sell the member information we provide to other third parties. 

In order to conduct business of the credit union, we may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you under other circumstances as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to process transactions on your behalf, conduct the operations of our credit union, follow your instructions as you authorize, or protect the security of our financial records. 

If you terminate your membership with Arizona State Savings & Credit Union, we will not share information we have collected about you, except as permitted or required by law. 

**

How We Protect Your Information 

**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who have a specific business purpose in utilizing your data. Our employees are trained in the importance of maintaining confidentiality and member privacy. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations and leading industry practices to safeguard your nonpublic personal information. 

**

What You Can Do to Help Protect Your Privacy 

**

Arizona State Savings & Credit Union is committed to protecting the privacy of its members. Members can help by following these simple guidelines: 

  * Protect your account numbers, card numbers, PINs (personal identification numbers) and passwords. Never keep your PIN with your credit or debit card which can provide free access to your account if your card is lost or stolen.

  * Use caution when disclosing your account numbers, social security numbers, etc. to other persons. If someone calls you, explains the call is on behalf of the credit union and asks for your account number, you should beware. Official credit union staff will have access to your information and will not need to ask for it.

  * Keep you information with us current.  It is important that we have current. information on how to reach you. If we detect potentially fraudulent or unauthorized activity or use of an account, we will attempt to contact you immediately. If your address or phone number changes, please let us know.

If you have any questions concerning this notice, please do not hesitate to call us – we are your financial partner. 

Arizona State Savings & Credit Union requires that all visitors to our site on the Internet (the "Site") adhere to the following rules and regulations.  Arizona State Savings & Credit Union maintains this Site to provide you with information about Arizona State Savings & Credit Union products and services and to facilitate communication with Arizona State Savings & Credit Union.

Your access to and use of the Site are subject to terms and conditions and all applicable laws and regulations.  From time to time we may revise these terms and conditions.

Copyright in the pages, screens, text and images appearing at the Site is owned by Arizona State Savings & Credit Union or others as stated.  You may copy information from the Site for personal or educational use only, provided that each copy includes any copyright, trademark, or service mark notice or attribution as they appear, on the pages copied.  The information and materials may not otherwise by copied, displayed, distributed,  downloaded, licensed, modified, published, reposted, reproduced, reused, sold, transmitted, used to create a derivative work or otherwise used for public or commercial purposes except as provided in these terms and conditions without the express WRITTEN permission of Arizona State Savings & Credit Union.

Unless otherwise required by applicable law, any communication or material you transmit to us via the Site or Internet electronic mail is on a non-confidential basis.  This is not a secure web site.

# # #
